

born January 27, 1982



address

43 – 100 Tychy street Morcinka 5/17





https://krzysztofa.pl



GitHub: https://github.com/ g-krzysztof

Krzysztof Gryc React FRONT-END DEVELOPER

For over ten years my work has been related to design, creating websites and programming in java script / type script.

I am currently working as a Senior React Developer.

I create, develop and maintain web projects based on React.

I am developing an editor project that is part of the back-office system of a media company.

The most important technologies and tools in the stack:

Typescript / React / Redux / Next.js / Storybook / Styled components Cypress / REST & graphQL

Career Summary

2021 to present Senior React Developer - Autentika

Creation, development and maintenance of web projects based on React. Most important projects:

- maintenance and development of the editor, which is part of the media company's back-office system
- design system and implementation of a project enabling the search for raw material areas

2019-2021 React developer - KATO Software House

Creating and developing the front-end layer of projects:

- website and administration panel for the parenting control application
- crypto currency website with an administration panel, purchase, investments, investment presentation

2014-2019 Front-end Developer - freelancer

Website creation: HTML, Sass, React.js Building CMS websites: Joomla, WordPress. Designing website layouts and graphic elements.

to **2014**

I worked as a computer graphic designer.
I created projects for the website and related to printing [DTP].

Education:

2003 - 2008 Full-time studies at the University of Silesia in Katowice
MA in Polish Philology – specialty: editing and textology

1997 – 2002 Electronics and Electrical Technical Secondary School in Tychy

technician – specialty: computer systems

Skills

Working in a team and independently on the front-end layer of websites and applications, testing code.

Building new projects. Maintenance, development, refactoring of existing projects.

Creating responsive websites.

Graphic design of layouts and website elements.

Code review.

Work in the kanban and agile methodology.

Deployment, continue integrations.

Working in the environment: Windows, IOS.

Writing e2e, unit and integration tests.

Working with language models and AI tools.

Stack & tools

I currently work in a stack:

I also worked with:

REACT

[redux, saga, react-query]

TypeScript

REST API & GraphQL

[Apollo server]

Styled Components, Styled

System, Sass [BEM]

Storybook, Figma

Next.js, NX monorepo, Strapi

Husky, Lerna, Prettier, Eslint

Gitlab, Jira, Slack, MS Teams

Cypress e2e, Jest,

React Testing Library

ratso worked with.

Strapi, Sanity [headless CMS]

Gatsby

Docker

Symphony, twig templates

Github, Bitbucket, Gitlab

PM2, Vercel, Heroku

Additional skills

- English at communicative level
- graphic design, photo processing and retouching
- ability to prepare projects for offset printing

Interests

Party role-playing games, board games.

I will be happy to provide references if needed.

+48 535 38 37 27 hello@krzysztofg.pl